Hello.
どうもこんにちは
How are you?
元 気でした?
I'm fine.
元気だって
It's been a while.
久しぶりだね
How many years has it been?
何年ぶりかな?
How many months has it been?
何ヶ月ぶりかな?
How many months?
何ヶ月
That's cool, it's cosplay after all.
やばいね、やっぱコスプレ
nice.
いいね
copper?
どう?
Try it on and wear bread.
着てみて、パン装
Would you like to try it on?
着てみて?
You think it suits you, right?
似合ってると思うでしょ?
I wonder if I can still go.
まだいけるかなって思う
Wow, this is really true.
やばい、これ本当に
JK, right?
JKでしょ?
This is a bit JK.
これはちょっとJKだよ
Wow, already.
すごい、もう
Seriously.
マジで
I think it suits you very well.
めっちゃ似合ってると思うよ
This is a little nice.
これちょっといい
Isn't it okay?
いいんじゃない?
Let's try it like this?
こういってみる?
With this.
これで
But somehow, it doesn't feel like a bad cosplay.
でもなんかさ、コスプレ感やばくないから
yes.
そう
Isn't that what sailor uniforms are all about?
セーラー服ってそんなもんじゃないの?
What is pocket?
ポッケは何?
fake?
偽物?
Cosplay?
コスプレ?
It's coming in.
入るじゃん
There's going to be cigarettes.
タバコ入るじゃん
You can become a Yankee.
ヤンキーになれるじゃん
nice.
いいね
Cosplay is crazy.
コスプレやべーな
The destructive power of cosplay is amazing.
や っぱコスプレの破壊力ってすごいね
As expected.
さすがだね
This is terrible.
これやばいわ
Awesome.
すげーわ
Wow, that's nice.
いやーいいね
What, you didn't wear it in high school?
え、高校の時着てないんでしょ?
Because.
だって
Is it a little different?
ちょっと違う?
Is it slightly different?
若干違う?
Yes, there's a version without the ribbon.
そう、なんかね、リボンがないバージョンって
Eh, what is that?
え、なにそれ?
Are the shapes the same?
形は一緒なの?
The shape looks like this.
形こんな感じ
picture?
え?
lie?
嘘?
Don't you have a ribbon?
リボンないの?
Inside the ribbon.
リボンの中
Ah, there is such a thing.
あ、そんなのあるんだ
That's amazing.
すごいな
Wow, it's amazing when you stand up.
いやー立つと、立つとすごいな
nice.
いいね
Wait a little crazy.
ちょっと狂って待ってみて
oh!
おー!
terrible.
やばい
Now that JK has turned.
JKが回った今
Please wait again slowly.
もう一回ゆっくり待ってみて
slowly?
ゆっくり?
oh!
おー!
That's amazing.
すげーな
I'm a perverted old man.
変 態おじさんだね、俺
Are you an uncle?
おじさんなの?
He's a pervert, let's go.
変態おじさんだよ、行くよ
Oh, wait this.
あ、待ってこれ
It's come, it's come.
来た来た
The feeling of the train shaking.
電車の揺れる感じ
Recreate it.
再現して
Electron is a tank.
電子がたんごとーん
It's a tango.
が たんごとーん
Open it again.
また開いて
Oh my god, this is so bad.
おーやばいやばい
This is bad.
これはまずい
That's terrible.
やばいわ
This place is bad, this place.
ここまずい、ここ
What is this?
これなにこれ?
picture?
え?
What's here?
ここなに?
picture?
え?
Here, let's have some fun.
ここなんか、チカンをさ、こう
Isn't this what you feel when you shake?
チカンするときこんな感じでしょ?
Have you ever been teased?
チカンされたことある?
It happens once.
一回ある
Is there one?
あるの?
Oh, is that so?
え、そうなの?
Also, while waiting for the elevator outside.
あと外でエレベーター待ってるとき
Has it broken?
切れた?
Then there's the elevator.
そ したらエレベーター
What did you say?
なんて言った?
I was listening to it with my earphones and I said something.
私イヤホン聞いてて、なんかえって言っちゃった
Then?
そしたら?
Then it went somewhere.
そしたらどっか行っちゃった
Why didn't you catch me?
なんで捕まえなかったの?
You'd be surprised.
びっくりするよね
Seriously?
まじで?
How did you touch me?
どうやって触られたの?
I heard a sound and stood there.
なんかこう、音が聞いて立ってて
What, when you were in high school?
え、高校のとき?
different.
違う
Was it a skirt?
スカートだった?
Was it in a skirt?
スカート入ってたの?
It had a skirt in it.
スカート入ってた
So?
それで?
So, while I was touching her like this, she came up to me from behind.
で、こうやって触ってて、後ろからスーってきて
What?
え、何?
Did you touch my pussy?
まんこ触られたの?
Yeah, I feel like I'm still human.
うん、なんかね、人ままとか
Did you touch me?
触られたの?
Didn't you just hit it?
当たっちゃったんじゃなくて?
Well, because it's like this.
え、だってこうで
Eh, what do you think?
え、どう?
This is what it looks like from behind.
後ろからこんな感じ
Touch it?
触って?
Yes, touch it.
そう、触って
Really?
本当に?
Can't you forgive me?
許せんの?
Have you forgiven me?
許しちゃったの?
I was only 18.
まだ18だったから
Oh, were you a little scared?
あ、ちょっと怖かったのか
I see.
そっか
Good, that person.
いいな、その人
That person is nice.
その人いいな
Butt, pop your butt out.
お尻、お尻プクって出して
Pui.
プイって
It feels like pui.
プイって感じ
Do you understand?
分かる?
I think I have a hard body.
私、体硬いと思うんだわ
Stick your butt out.
お尻をキュッと出して
Ah, good, good.
あ、いい、いい
I can see your pants.
パンツ見えてるよ
You can see my pants.
パンツ見えてるやつじゃん
Okay, leave it as is.
いいよ、そのまま
I can see your back.
背 中 見えてる
This is terrible.
やばい、これ
I feel like I want to go from here.
ここから行きたくなっちゃうような感じだね
Ah, it feels like this.
ああ、こういう感じね
It's like this.
こういう感じ
I can see your back.
背中見えてる
背中見えちゃってる
picture?
え?
Um, Glow?
あれ、グロウ?
No bra?
ノーブラ?
Can't go, braless?
行けないの、ノーブラ?
picture?
え?
terrible.
やばい
I like this touch.
いいね、この触り心地
You're still young.
まだ若いね
Although my back is completely visible.
背中丸見えなんだけど
That's dangerous, isn't it?
やばいでしょ
That's amazing though.
すごいんだけど
Full back view.
背中丸見え
Pants are fully visible.
パンツ丸見え
These pants are nice too.
このパンツもいいね
nice.
いいね
That's good.
いいっすね
You took off your mask.
マスク取ったね
I took it.
取った
Nice, that's it.
いいね、それは
She looks quite JK-ish.
かなりJKっぽいわ
She has a JK feel.
JK感あるよ
be?
ある?
Look here.
こっち見て
nice.
いいね
It's kind of like that.
なんか、あれだね
I feel like I'm a high school student.
高校生になった感じする、俺
If you look like this, it's like you're a couple.
こんな感じだと、なんかさ、 カップルでさ、
Come to my boyfriend's room, you know?
自分の彼氏の部屋とか来てさ、 わかるかな?
That's what it feels like.
そんな感じ
Do you understand?
わかる?
I'll go home once, change my clothes, and go.
一回家帰ってさ、着替えてさ、 行くじゃん
Well, it's about clothes.
して、服ってことじゃん
After school, I went straight to my boyfriend's house.
学校帰りに、そのまま彼氏の家に来てさ、
I guess this is how you look at the camera.
こういうカメラ目線なんだろうな、
perhaps.
多分
Subjectively.
主観的には
Just say it today, please.
ちゃんと今日言ってね、ちょっと
What?
なんよ
Make my pussy a mess.
私のおまんこをぐっちゃぐちゃにしてって
picture?
え?
Can you say it?
言える?
Just say it.
ちょっと言ってみて
I already want a cock.
もう、チンポが欲しいとか
It's called India.
インドってやつ
イ ンドってやつ
Do you know what India is?
インドってやつ、わかる?
Then, for a moment, think of this camera as your boyfriend.
じゃあちょっと、 このカメラが彼氏だと思って
This is because it's my boyfriend.
これ、彼氏だから
boyfriend?
彼氏?
I've been spending the last few hours with my boyfriend.
これもう、 この数時間をちょっと彼氏で
good?
いい?
It's my boyfriend.
彼氏だよ
What should I do?
どうする?
Golden boyfriend.
金彼氏
No, my boyfriend is right in front of me.
いや、 彼氏が目の前にいるよ
Well then, I'll speak on behalf of my boyfriend.
じゃあ、俺、彼氏の代わりに喋るね
How was school today?
今日、学校どうだった?
Did you take Mr. Tanaka's class?
田中先生の授業受けた?
I received it.
受けた
What score did you get on the test?
テスト、何点だった?
test, 80;
テスト、80
You're really smart.
めっちゃ頭いいね
I feel smart.
頭いいなって
That's amazing.
すごいな
I probably got around 30 points.
俺、多分30点くらいだったから、
You may lose units.
単位を落とすかもしれない
It's a red dot.
赤点だよ
Please tell me a little bit.
ちょっと教えてよ
Professor Tanaka's class.
田中先生の授業
Physical education, or rather, sex education class.
体育の、体育というか、性教育の授業
Was it PE?
体育だった?
This time, it's about sex.
今回は、 性の話じゃん
It was a test about sexuality.
性についてのテストだったじゃん
Eggs and life and death.
卵子と生死が
That's amazing.
すごいね
Why don't you know?
なんで分かんの?
Isn't it amazing?
すごくない?
why?
なんで?
Do you know more?
詳しいの?
I research every day.
毎日研究してる
what?
何?
Are you doing research?
研究してるの?
Eggs and life and death are also a little bit of practice.
卵子と生死が実践するのもちょっと
Properly in the video.
動画でちゃんと
Maybe YouTube.
YouTubeかなんかね
That's amazing.
すごいね
Are you going to try it?
試したりするの?
I have to try it.
試さないと
What kind of research is there?
どういう研究ない?
There isn't.
ないよ
Are you a little curious?
ちょっと気になる?
There isn't.
ないよ
Also, I heard it from my parents.
あと親から聞いたりとか
Do you hear from your parents?
親から聞くの?
Is that what you talk about?
そういう話すんの?
Why do you ask me where I was born?
なんで私が生まれたのとか聞くの?
What did you say then?
そしたら何て言ってたの?
You mean father?
お父さんってこと?
Me and my dad, what?
私と、 お父さんが、 何?
A little bit at night.
夜ちょっとね
Look at the threads.
糸並みをね
Line of thread?
糸並み?
yes.
そう
I pressed it and it came out by mistake.
押して、 間違って出しちゃって、
The child who was born by mistake was me.
間違って出して生まれた子が自分って、
Isn't she quite an accomplished child?
かなり、 でき ちゃった子んじゃないの?
yes.
そう
It's been popular lately.
最近流行ってる
What did you think when you heard that?
それ聞いてどう思ったの?
I thought it was serious.
マジかと思った
マジかと思っちゃった
So, for the time being, I will study the threads.
それで、 と りあえず糸並みの勉強は、
You completed it.
コンプリートしたのね
What about actual combat?
実戦とかは?
As for the actual battle.
実戦はね
Don't you have any actual battles?
実戦はしないの?
I don't decide.
決めしない
Aren't you going to have a real fight?
実戦しないの?
I got a bad score, so I'd like you to tell me a little bit about it.
俺、点数悪かったからさ、 ちょっと教えてほしいんだよね
Okay.
いいよ
I was wondering what I should do.
どうすればいいのかなって
Like the strings of the night.
夜の糸並みとか
My father is strict, so I can't listen to him.
俺、お父さん厳しいからさ、 聞けないんだよね
Because I think I'll get angry.
怒られそうだから
How do you do it?
どうやってやってんの?
everytime.
いつも
How do I do it?
どうやってやるのかな?
How do we do it?
どうやってやるんだろう?
I don't know.
分からないんだよね
I wonder how they'll do it.
どうやってやるんだろうね
I've never seen boobs before.
おっぱいとか見たことないから、俺
I've never seen it before.
見たことない
Do you have boobs?
おっぱいあるの?
Wait, if it's not there, it's a man.
待って、なかったら男だ
There it is for now.
とりあえずある
Is there one?
あるの?
Yeah.
ええ
I want you to tell me the threads of the night.
夜の糸並み教えてほしい
That's nice.
いいな
Like, really.
いいね、本当に
This is because he's my boyfriend.
これ、彼氏だからね
OK?
boyfriend.
彼氏
This is my boyfriend.
彼氏だよ、これ
What should I do?
どうする?
I want you to tell me the threads of the night.
夜の糸並み教えてほしい
picture?
え?
What does the string look like at night?
夜の糸並みは、 どんな感じ?
picture?
え?
Why do you hate it?
なんで嫌がるの?
Look.
ほら
Hey, lips.
ちょっと、唇
my lips
俺の唇
With my lips.
俺の唇で
The threads of the night.
夜の糸並み
Later, my mom will be there.
後、お母さんいるからそこに
Wait a minute, if your mom was there, you wouldn't be able to have this conversation.
ちょっと待って、お母さんいたらこんな話できないじゃん
Are you in the next room?
隣 の部屋にいるの?
Yes, I'm in the next room, right now.
そう、隣の部屋にいる、今
Hey, lips.
ちょっと、唇
Show me your lips.
唇見せて
I want to see your lips.
唇見たいな
Lips, just a little.
唇、ちょっと、ちょっと
Why do you hate it so much?
なんでそんなに嫌がるの?
Aren't we dating?
俺たち付き合ってるんじゃないの?
How many days have you been together?
付き合ってまだ何日?
It's only been about a year.
まだ1年くらい
picture?
え?
It's not a year.
1年じゃない
The threads of the night.
夜の糸並み
I really hate it.
めっちゃ嫌がってるやん
Hey, lips.
ちょっと、唇
This is what my mom asked me to do.
お母さん聞いてるから、これ
Show me your lips.
唇見せて
lips.
唇
Hey, hey, hey.
ちょっと、ちょっと、ちょっと
lips.
唇
Eh, won't you give me a chew?
え、チューしてくんないの?
You do it all the time.
いつもしてるんじゃん
So, what about today?
じゃあ、今日は?
Is it bad today?
今日はダメなの?
You might be able to hear your mother's voice through the walls.
お母さんの声って壁で聞いてるかも
Well then, I understand.
じゃあ、分かった
Well then, I'll stick to my breasts.
じゃあ、おっぱいで我慢するね
picture?
え?
Is it Mobra?
モーブラなの?
everytime.
いつも
Are you a mobra at school?
学校でモーブラなの?
My boobs are coming out.
おっぱい出てきちゃったよ
amazing.
すごい
Hey, look here.
ちょっと、こっち見て
terrible.
やばい
Your boobs are amazing.
おっぱいすごい
That's terrible.
やばいね
Okay, then the boyfriend game is over.
よし、じゃあ彼氏ゲーム終了ね
Let's get serious here.
ちょっと、ここから真面目に
Seriously a little bit.
真面目にちょっと
Shall I feel it?
感じていこうか
It's strange to take it so seriously.
真面目に感じていこうかっておかしい
Have your breasts gotten bigger?
おっぱい大きくなったの?
No, this one and this one.
違う、こっちとこっち
The sides are different.
サイド違うよ
They're different sizes.
大きさ違うね
This one is small.
こっち小さい
This one is big.
こっちのが大きい
Isn't there about D here?
こっちDくらいあるんじゃない?
Is there any?
あるかな?
This B?
こっちB?
C Where is it?
Cどこにあるんだろう?
Isn't there about D here?
こっちDくらいあるんじゃない?
Why is it so different?
なんでこんなに違うの?
Because the one with the heart is on the right.
心臓ある方が右だから
The heart is on the left.
心臓ある方が左だよ
Why?
なんでだろう?
why?
なんで?
Is the tube tickling?
チューブくすぐったいんだっけ?
tickles.
くすぐったい
What about the tube?
チューブは?
Where do you feel it?
どこ感じるの?
The tube is so pink.
チューブすげえピンク
It's amazingly pink.
す げえピンクだ
It's so pink.
すごいピンクだよ
It was cold.
冷たかったよ
It's cold, isn't it?
冷たいでしょ
terrible.
やばい
My neck is terrible.
首 や ばい
I can see your pants.
パンツ見えちゃう
That's amazing.
すごいね
Well, let me out here for a second.
じゃあ ちょっとこっち出して
Can you bring me more?
もっとこっち出してきていい?
Butt.
お尻
This is erotic.
エロいなこれ
It's erotic.
エロいよ
What's wrong with Tenma?
テンマがダメなんだっけ?
Is Tenma weak?
テンマ弱いんだっけ?
Tenma is weak.
テンマ弱いんだよ
Is it no good?
ダメなの?
But you know, if it's over your pants, wouldn't it be better to split it?
でもほら、ズボンの上からだったら 割り方いいんじゃない?
comparatively?
割り方?
How to split hold a little.
割り方ちょっと持って
Isn't that a good way to divide it?
割り方いいんじゃない?
If it's over your pants.
ズボンの上だったら
I'll come over in a bit.
ちょっとやってくるよ
Well then, Kyo-san, I'm safe after all.
じゃあきょうさん、俺やっぱセーフだからさ
You know, it's safe.
ほら、セーフだからさ
Right here?
ここでしょ?
What do you say here?
ここ何て言うの?
Um, chestnut...
えっと、クリ...
Eh, here?
え、ここ?
this?
これ?
What do you say here?
ここ何て言うの?
Clear...
クリ...
What is chestnut?
クリ何?
Clear...
クリ...
clitoris?
クリトリス?
Clitoris?
ク リトリス?
So, here?
じゃあ、ここ?
Here, um, what do you say?
ここはね、えっと、何て言うの?
hole?
穴?
here.
ここ
Does it start with okara?
おから始まる?
What do you say about this overall?
これ全体的に何て言うの?
oh?
お?
何個?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Oh, you said it.
おー、言えたじゃん
That's 100 points.
100点だね
100 points on the sex education test.
性教育のテスト100点
There are 100 points.
100点があるよ
Is this the only one you can open?
これしか開ける?
Yeah, but what about the phone?
え、でも電話はどうなの?
Doesn't it feel good?
気持ちよくない?
The phone...
電話は...
If it was weak.
弱だったら
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
Like this?
こんな感じ?
What does it feel like?
どんな感じなの?
I mean, does it feel good like this?
なんかね、こんな感じ気持ちいいの?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
気持ちいいの?
Strain your hands.
手をこして
Show me your breasts with your hands.
手でおっぱいちょっと見せて
where are your boobs?
おっぱいどこにあるの?
nice.
いいね
This is amazing.
すごいよ、これ
It's so erotic.
めっちゃエロいよ
It's very erotic.
すごくエロいよ
This is correct.
これ、当たってるよ
Where is it right?
どこが当たってるよ
Which is better?
どこがいい?
どこがいいって
Where do you get it right?
どこが当たってます?
That's right.
当たってる
terrible.
やばい
It's very accurate.
めっちゃ当たってる
That's right.
当たってる
I don't care.
どうだって
You must have been a little worried today, haven't you?
今日はね、 ちょっと 悩んできたんじゃないの?
Because I brought it.
持っとくってだから
It's okay because it won't fall.
落ちないから大丈夫
Oh, pants.
おー、パンツ
Today, I'm going to use this guy.
今日はね、こいつ使ってくんだ
He's my buddy.
相棒だよ
It's kind of crazy.
なんかめっちゃ
JK's pussy.
JKのマンコ
Oh, your pussy is so small.
あら、マンコちっちゃいね
Don't play with this.
これで遊ばないでよ
I can see your whole pussy.
マンコ丸見えるよ
Look.
ほら
I can see her whole pussy.
マンコ丸見える
So let's take this off.
じゃあこれ脱いじゃおう
Okay, leave it like this.
いいよ、このままで
Good.
よいしょ
So what's going on inside your pants?
じゃあパンツの裏を、 どうなってるか
Isn't it dirty?
汚れてない?
Where is the back of your pants?
どこパンツの裏?
where?
どこ?
tell me.
教えて
Isn't it clean?
汚れてなくね?
Not dirty.
汚れてない
Did you spit it back?
吐き返ってきたの?
I'm not spitting it back.
吐き返ってないよ
why?
なんで?
There's nothing attached.
何も付いてないじゃん
why?
なん で?
なんで?
Why?
なんでって
Why isn't it dirty?
なんで汚れないの?
It feels very clean.
清潔感たっぷりだね
That's amazing.
すごいね
Look, I can see your pussy.
マンコほら、見えちゃった
Oh no, look at this.
やばい、これほら
It feels like a JK's pussy.
JKのマンコって感じ
Her breasts are very pink.
おっぱいすごいピンク
It's so pink.
すごいピンクだわ
this?
これ?
here?
ここ?
this?
これ?
What is this?
これ何?
clitoris.
クリトリス
Is this Kuri-chan?
これクリちゃん?
Is it Kuri-chan?
クリちゃんなの?
Kuri-chan is nice.
クリちゃんいいね
Kuri-chan.
クリちゃんさ
This is a bit of a nuisance.
これちょっと邪魔だわ
Let's end this.
これで終わりといて
Kuri-chan.
クリちゃん
amazing.
すごい
A tight pussy.
パックリのマンコ
I really like this angle.
このアングルすごい好きなんだよね
Move your hand a little.
ちょっと手移動げて
Show me your hands and boobs.
手おっぱいちょっと見せて
nice.
いいね
Camera boyfriend.
カメラ彼氏
It's over now.
もうそれ終わったんだ
That's amazing.
すごいね
Where does it feel good?
どこが気持ちいい?
Inside.
中と
Chestnut.
クリ
Both?
どっちも?
Is this still dangerous?
これでもやばいかな
What about directly?
直接は?
Above?
上のほう?
Above.
上のほう
Chestnut...
クリは...
Your clitoris is the type that hurts if you apply too much pressure, right?
クリは当てすぎると痛くなるタイプでしょ?
Well then, you've reached your limit.
じゃあ限界になったりいってね
That's right.
当たってるよ
picture?
え?
Today, we're going to do something even more amazing.
今日はね、もっとすごいのやっていくからね
Today is.
今日は
So far, I've done it before.
ここまではね、前もね、 やったんだけどね
Today, I want you to wet your pussy a little more.
今日はちょっとね、 もうちょっとマンコを 濡らして
picture?
え?
what?
何?
Are you ticklish?
くすぐったいの?
tickles.
くすぐったい
tickles?
くすぐったい?
It tickles, it tickles.
くすぐったいね、くすぐったい
Are you ticklish?
くすぐったいの?
why?
なんで?
Try making it a little stronger.
もうちょっと強くしてみて
No way.
やだ
tickles.
くすぐったい
No?
だめ?
Really.
ほんとに
what?
何?
Really, really.
ほんと、ほんと
No?
だめなの?
I've done this before.
前もこんなことしたな
nice.
いいね
No, but it's very erotic.
いや、でもすごいエロいね
Well then, open your pussy wide open for yourself.
じゃあ、マンコ、自分でパックリ開いてよ
Open your pussy wide open.
マンコ、パックリ開いて
Hey, just a little about yourself.
ほ ら、自分でちょっと
Oh yeah, keep it open.
そうそう、開いててね
Look here.
こっち見てね
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Please watch it.
見ててね
Kuri-chan.
クリちゃん
Chestnut-chan, crunchy.
ク リ ちゃん、コリコリ
Amazing pussy, beautiful.
すごいマンコ、綺麗
Give me more, here.
もっとちょうだい、こっち
Ah, yes, yes.
あ、そうそうそう
Please open it.
開いてね
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
this.
これ
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
Kuri-chan, hear me.
クリちゃん、聞こえて
Kuri-chan, pinpoint.
クリちゃん、ピンポイントで
picture?
え?
It's spot on.
ピンポイントで当たってるよ
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
something.
何か
What does it feel like?
どんな感じなの?
this.
これ
cold.
冷たい
picture?
え?
Is it cold?
冷たいの?
In the warmth.
温かい中
It's so warm.
すごい温かい
What's it like around here?
この辺、どんな感じ?
What does it feel like?
どんな感じなの?
this.
これ
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
I'm really lazy here.
すごいダラダラしてるよ、ここ
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
something.
何か
Does Kinko feel better?
キンコの方が気持ちいい?
Does the penis feel better?
おキンコの方が気持ちいい?
Do you like kinkin?
おキンキン好きなの?
I like kinkin.
おキンキン好き
Do you like Okinkin?
お キ ン キ ン 好き?
Okay, then let's take a look at her pussy.
よし、じゃあちょっと、おまんこ見ていこうかな
I'll take a look.
ちょっと見ていくよ